X-Mas array
X-MAS ARRAY
Problem Statement
"An array is called ""X-Mas"", if no two adjacent elements have sum strictly greater than X."
You are given an array A of N integers. In one operation you can select a K {1<=K<=N) such that AK > 0 and decrease AK by 1.
"For the given value of X, find the minimum number of"
"operations required to make A, a X-Mas array. You are given T independent test cases."
Constraints
1<= T <= 10
1<= N <= 105
1<= Ai<= 109
0 <= x <= 109
